Guide to the Clifford K. Berryman cartoon collection, 1899-1949 MS2024
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- "The 'Numbers' Is Such A Harmless Little Game", undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  shows Laws, an unidentified figure and Pine with clubs, beating snakes "Bribery" "Gangsterism" and "Jury Fixing" that slither out of the courthouse
- "Speaking Of Hot Dogs-", Circa 1938 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  shows Congress on a treadmill marked "Social Security Amendment" "Tax Revision" "Neutrality" and "Relief"; Franklin D. Roosevelt holds out a hot dog marked "Adjournment" and tells Congress "Step Faster, Old Fellow, If You Want It"
- "The Helping Hand (Modern Version)", undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  shows old fisherman "Farm Relief" helping little girl "Congress" to row a boat
- "John Bull Hasn't Recognized It Yet", undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  shows Uncle Sam and teddy bear helping "J. Bull" to see the "Panama Republic" through their binoculars and magnifying glass
- "Uncle Sam- I Hope They Won't Be Too Tired To Return For My Little Blowout Next Month", undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  shows crowds running "To The Coronation"; Uncle Sam stands by with a flag and rockets, and teddy bear is shimmying up the flag staff
- No title, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  shows Uncle Sam between two farmers urging him to buy and not to buy their wheat; teddy bear shrinks under Sam's money bags as he comments "By Jinks This Is Gettin Embarrassing"
- No title, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  shows farmer looking at a picture of teddy bear and Uncle Sam enjoying a rain storm; he comments "Oh Boy! Equalization Fees And Export Debenture Would Have Nothin' On This For Relief!"
- No title, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  shows Norris holding up the placard "Boulder Dam Legislation" as "One Of The Best Things Congress Has Ever Done"; Uncle Sam comments "Hooray! Now I Know It's Christmas!" and teddy bear cheers
- No title, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  shows "Dr. Jimmy Cox" offering Uncle Sam "Democratic Tariff Bitters" as the "Only Relief"; teddy bear gasps and Uncle Sam refuses, saying "Thanks Doc. I've Tried It!"
- No title, Circa 1946 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  shows Stalin Showing Franco to Truman and Atlee, and saying "I Demand That Something Be Done About That Fellow. He's A Threat To World Peace"
- "Squash Center Hears Of Some Words Now Current In Washington", undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  shows locals gathered around a stove, reading words such as "Disingenuous" "Fustian" and "Bumblepuppy"
- "Note- Fight Promoter Rickard Contends That Radio Keeps Fight Fans At Home", undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  shows Rickard on the floor crying "Foul!" against a radio wearing boxing gloves
- "St. Valentine's Day", undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  shows Congress running away after leaving mean messages at the U.S. Supreme Court's door
- No title, Circa 1937 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  shows "Doctors" Franklin D. Roosevelt, Minton, and Norris laying the Supreme Court out on an examination table; they comment "We Merely Wish To Find Out Just What's The Matter With You!"
- No title, Circa 1939 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  shows Franklin D. Roosevelt telling Congress to "separate" the mixed cattle in the "U S Business Pen"; Congress replies "Chief, I'd Rather Try To Balance The Budget"
- "Followed Her Into The House Like A String Of Sheep", undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  shows military men being led into a house by a woman
- No title, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  shows Davis, Cox and Smith in the office of "Dr. E.X. Aminer" who tells them "You've All Suffered From Bryanitis But Only One OF You Shows Symptoms Of Another Attack"
- No title, Circa 1928 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  shows Smith and McAdoo with a pickaxe and hoe, digging up earth; a placard reads "President Coolidge Sticks To Worms To Catch 'Em"
- No title, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  shows Robinson and Smith riding donkeys labeled "Wet Democracy" and "Dry Democracy"; Robinson comments "We Must Find Some Way To Turn This Animal Around"
- "Practice", undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  shows Smith and McAdoo rolling snowballs
- No title, Circa 1946 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  shows Molotov and Stalin viewing Gromyko and a parade of the UNO, and commenting "Everybody's Out Of Step But Our Boy Andrei"
- "News Note- A Painting Hanging Sideways Won A Second Prize Award Recently", undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  shows the Senate holding up a painting of elephants and donkeys wrestling amid placards marked "Old Guard" "Democracy" etc
- No title, Circa 1946 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  shows Marshall telling Truman "The Russians Are Strange People- It's Hard To Get Them To Agree On Anything"; in the background is the Capitol Building fuming with "Budget Disagreement" "Clash On Taxes"; "Labor Legislation Row" and "Appropriations Fight"